Welcome to this section! I'm really excited
Bienvenido a esta seccin! Estoy muy emocionado por
for this section, because it is one of my passions.
esta seccin, porque es una de mis pasiones.
I have a number of other courses on this, and I think you're really going
Tengo varios otros cursos sobre esto, y creo
to love learning about Flask and web development
que realmente te encantar aprender sobre Flask y
with Python.
desarrollo web con Python.
In this section
En esta
we're going to be giving users engaging
seccin vamos a ofrecer a los usuarios
content, getting data back from them,
contenido interesante, recuperar datos de ellos
and presenting everything in a nice, easy to use
y presentar todo de una manera agradable
fashion. Flask is excellent for that.
y fcil de usar. Frasco es excelente para eso.
And Python is a really strong language for doing all
Y Python es un lenguaje realmente fuerte para hacer todo
sorts of web development as a whole.
tipo de desarrollo web en general.
Even from its use of decorators and database interactions,
Incluso desde el uso de decoradores y las interacciones de
all the way up to asynchronous development,
bases de datos, hasta el desarrollo asincrnico, Python es un
Python is a great language to do this sort of stuff.
gran lenguaje para hacer este tipo de cosas.
With that said, I'll see you on the next video
Dicho esto, te ver en el siguiente video